互联网上的网站多如牛毛
The internet has billions of websites.
其中一些却总能让你满腹狐疑
Some leave you with a lot of questions.
它们藏着神秘代码，诡异倒计时，骇人录音等等
They contain secret codes, strange countdowns, creepy recordings, and more.
今天，我们就来一场网络奇谈之旅，从拉到夯，逐一揭秘那些最神秘的网站
Today we'll explore the internet's most mysterious websites starting from the least to the most disturbing.
伙计们，我今年的目标是在不牺牲质量的前提下，提高更新频率
So my goal this year guys is to increase our uploads without sacrificing quality
而这需要我们共同成长
and to do that we got to keep growing.
如果你能订阅我的频道，那将是我最大的荣幸，我保证
It would mean the world to me if you subscribed and I promise
会竭尽全力，为你们创作出最棒的视频
to do my very best for you guys and make the best videos I possibly can.
我是VisualVenture，而你，我的朋友，帅呆了
I'm VisualVenture and you my friend are awesome.
LakeCityQuietPills.com
LakeCityQuietPills.com.
“湖城静心丸”网站，听起来像个药店，但它卖的却不是药
LakeCityQuietPills.com sounds like a pharmacy website, but it wasn't selling medicine.
实际上，人们相信这里是职业杀手接收任务指令的秘密据点
In fact, people believed this website was a place where hitmen received instructions on who to target.
这个网站的主人是一位名叫Milo的Reddit用户
The site belonged to a Reddit user known as Milo.
Milo自称是位79岁的退伍老兵
Milo claimed he was a 79-year-old military vet.
他在Reddit上的帖子大多与武器，炸药和战斗有关
Most of his Reddit posts were about weapons, explosives, and combat.
然后在2009年5月，他发帖宣传了自己的新网站
Then in May 2009, he made a post promoting his new website.
就是这个LakeCityQuietPills.com
LakeCityQuietPills.com.
他声称这只是个图片托管网站
He described it as an image hosting site.
起初，根本没人在意
Now first, no one cared.
但多年后，终于有人发现了端倪
But years later, someone finally looked closer.
一位Reddit网友点开了链接，并察觉到了异样
A Redditor clicked the link and noticed something strange.
他向其他人发出了警告
He warned others.
还记得那个老头的图床吗
Remember that old guy's image host?
去网站根目录看看源代码
Go to the root of the site and view source.
人们真去看了
People did exactly that.
当他们检查网站代码时，竟在代码的字里行间发现了天书般的加密信息
When they checked the site's code, they discovered cryptic messages hidden between the lines of code.
这些信息看起来像是招聘启事
They looked like job postings.
其中一条写着，急需
One read, immediate need.
8-10名华人或韩国人
8-10 Chinese or Korean.
韩语方言或口音流利
Fluent Korean dialect or accent.
签约后详谈
Details after contract.
另一条则说招意大利或西班牙语者
Another said for Italian or Spanish speakers.
不要欧洲白人做“湿活”
No Euro W/W.
必须身家清白
Must be bondable.
Reddit最爱解谜了
Reddit loves a mystery.
于是用户们开始逐行分析，试图破解其中奥秘
So users started analyzing every line trying to figure out what it meant.
越读下去，感觉越是黑暗
And the more they read, the darker it seemed.
这看起来可不像什么正经工作
These didn't look like normal jobs.
倒像是招募刺客的黑话
They looked like requests for assassins.
这理论听着挺离谱，但人们之所以相信，原因如下
It was a wild theory, but here's why people believed it.
网站名叫“湖城静心丸”
The site was called, Lake City Quiet Pills.
密苏里州真有一家叫“湖城”的工厂
There's a real factory in Missouri called Lake City.
那是一家为美军生产子弹的弹药厂
It's an ammunition plant that manufactures bullets for the US military.
一些人认为“静心丸”就是子弹的代号
Some people thought quiet pills was code for bullets.
因为一颗子弹就像一粒能让人永远安静的药丸
Because a bullet is like a pill that makes someone quiet forever.
他们还解读了招聘信息中的暗语
They also interpreted the job listings.
信息里的“W/W”很可能指“湿活”
W/W in the messages likely meant wet work.
而“湿活”可能是暗杀行动的俚语
And wet work could be slang for assassination.
更多人分享了对其他缩写的猜想
More people shared ideas on what the other abbreviations could mean.
一点一滴，理论逐渐成形
Piece by piece, the theory took shape.
Reddit网友们愈发坚信，这就是一个杀手的秘密任务发布板
Redditors became convinced this was a secret job board for hitmen.
这听起来似乎有些牵强
It seemed like a stretch.
但随后发生的一件事，让这个理论的可信度大大增加
Then something happened that made the theory feel more credible.
2010年1月19日，一名军事领导人在迪拜被暗杀
On January 19th, 2010, a military leader was assassinated in Dubai.
此处2019应为作者失误，被刺杀者为哈马斯领导人马哈茂德·马巴胡赫
大约在同一时间，网友们在网站上发现了一条新消息
Around the same time, Redditors found a new message on the website.
上面写着，大家新年快乐
It read, Happy New Year everyone.
我们要在19号为老爷子办一场生日派对
We're having a birthday party for the old man on the 19th.
派对下午三点在老地方开始
Party starts at 1500 at the usual.
请回复给Shade确认是否参加
Send your RSVP to Shade.
另外，我们会为外地来的朋友预订三天的房间
FYI, we're booking a room for three days for anyone coming from out of area.
本地的朋友则安排一晚住宿
And overnight for locals.
一起来为“荷兰人”Milo举杯吧
Come hoist one for Dutch Milo.
这场派对的日期，与暗杀行动的日期完全吻合
The date of this party matched the exact day of the hit.
同一条消息还提到了预订三天的酒店
The same message also mentioned booking a hotel for three days.
有趣的是，那位军事领导人正是在一家酒店内遇害的
Interestingly, the military leader was unalived at a hotel.
一份报告是这样描述的
One report described it like this.
一群刺客追踪哈马斯领导人到他的房间
A group of assassins tracked the Hamas leader to his room,
等他出门购物时
waited for him to leave to go shopping,
潜入他的房间并以某种方式进入，然后等待目标返回
snuck into his room and gained access somehow and waited for the guy to come back
最后将他干掉
and lastly took him out.
对于Reddit的侦探们来说，这绝非巧合
For Reddit's detectives, this was no coincidence.
几周后，网站上又出现了一条新消息
Weeks later, another message appeared on the site.
它公布了1月19日那场派对的最终开销
It showed the final costs for the party that took place on January 19th.
酒店房间，豪车，巴士，餐饮，医疗用品
Hotel rooms, limo, bus, food, med supplies.
一场生日派对，光是酒店房间就花了将近5万美元
They spent nearly $50,000 on hotel rooms for a birthday.
在Reddit用户看来，这个数字更像是一笔黑暗交易的酬金
For Reddit users, the number looked like a payment for something much darker.
随着越来越多的人前来调查，网站开始发生变化
As more people investigated, the site began to change.
网站上曾经可读的信息，被搅乱成了一堆随机的数字和字母
The once readable messages on the site were scrambled into random numbers and letters.
到了2014年，LakeCityQuietPills.com彻底下线了
And by 2014, LakeCityQuietPills.com went offline completely.
它真的是一个杀手任务板，还是仅仅一个恶作剧
Was it really a hitman job board or was it just a prank?
时至今日，无人知晓确切答案
To this day, no one knows for sure.
下一个网站，则试图颠覆我们对世界的认知
This next website tried to change how we understand the world.
TimeCube.com
TimeCube.com.
TimeCube.com的创建，是为了向世界揭示一个惊天秘密
TimeCube.com was created to reveal a big secret to the world.
网站的主人是一位名叫Gene Ray的退休电工
The website belonged to a retired electrician named Gene Ray.
而Ray坚信自己发现了一个宇宙的奥秘
And Ray believed he uncovered a cosmic secret.
在他看来，一天并非24小时
According to him, a single day wasn't really 24 hours.
每一天实际上是四个独立的日子同时发生
Each day was actually four separate days happening at once.
我知道，这很难理解
It's confusing. I know.
Ray在网站上大胆地陈述着他的理论
Ray stated his theory boldly on the site.
他称之为“自然谐波同步四日时间立方”
He called it nature's harmonic simultaneous four-day time cube.
Ray甚至自诩为地球上最智慧的人
Ray even called himself the wisest man on earth.
他自信满满，悬赏1000美元
He was so confident that he offered $1,000
给任何能反驳“地球每次自转包含四天”理论的人
to anyone who can disprove four days in each earth rotation.
后来，他又把赏金提高到了1万美元
Later, he raised the price to $10,000.
他的网站充斥着关于“四角竞赛”
His website was packed with strange diagrams about four-corner races
和一种他称之为“立方思维”的奇怪图表
and something he called cubic thinking.
这看起来就像一个妄想症老头的胡言乱语
It looked like the ramblings of a delusional old man.
但并非所有人都对他置之不理
But not everyone ignored him.
事实上，麻省理工学院的学生还邀请他去做演讲
In fact, students at MIT invited him to speak.
2002年，Ray现身麻省理工，展示他的时间理论
In 2002, Ray showed up at MIT to present his theory of time.
数百人到场围观
Hundreds showed up.
但他们可不是来学习的
But they weren't there to learn.
他们把这场讲座当成了一场喜剧秀
They treated the lecture like a comedy show.
整场活动中，这群大学生喧闹不已，时常以一种戏谑的方式为Ray欢呼
Throughout the event, the crowd of college students was rowdy and loud, cheering often in mock support of Ray.
然而，Ray并未察觉他们是在嘲笑自己
However, Ray didn't realize they were mocking him.
事后被问及这次经历时，他吹嘘道
When asked about the experience later, he bragged.
大概有500名来自麻省理工，哈佛和周边许多大学的学生
About 500 students from MIT, Harvard, and many other universities around there.
他们现在待我如爱因斯坦
And they treat me like Einstein now.
之后，他甚至给自己颁发了“立方主义”博士学位
Afterward, he even awarded himself a doctorate of cubism
并开始自称Gene Ray博士
and started calling himself Dr. Gene Ray.
大多数人把Ray当成一个笑话
Most people treated Ray as a joke.
但对一个人来说，Gene Ray是个天才
But to one man, Gene Ray was a genius.
2005年前后，一位名叫Richard的18岁学生发现了timecube.com
Around 2005, an 18-year-old student named Richard discovered timecube.com.
他迅速成为Gene Ray最忠实的拥护者
He quickly became Gene Ray's most devoted supporter.
嗨，我是Richard Jankowski，第二聪明的人
Hi, I'm Richard Jankowski, second wisest human.
不过，地球上最聪明的人是立方大师，Gene Ray博士
However, it is Dr. Gene Ray, Cubic, who is the wisest human on Earth.
两年来，Richard一直在捍卫Ray的时间理论
For two years, Richard defended Ray's theory of time.
事实上，他简直把Ray奉为神明
In fact, he idolized Ray.
然后在2007年，Richard买了张去佛罗里达的机票，去见他的英雄
Then in 2007, Richard bought a plane ticket to Florida to meet his hero.
他计划拍摄一部关于Ray及其思想的纪录片
He planned to film a documentary about Ray and his ideas.
起初，一切都很顺利
At first, everything went well.
他们共度的两天里，一直在谈论timecube.com
The two days they spent together, they talked about timecube.com.
然后他们之间产生了误会
Then they had a misunderstanding.
Ray对Richard大发雷霆
Ray got really mad at Richard.
愤怒到在自己的网站上公开谴责他
So mad that he publicly denounced him on Ray's website.
对于Richard来说，这种被抛弃的感觉是毁灭性的
For Richard, the rejection was devastating.
在多年的忠诚之后，他的偶像却与他反目
After years of loyalty, his idol turned against him.
Richard从未真正释怀
Richard never really got over it.
看着他们的故事，你会意识到Richard和Ray在这些毫无意义的理论上浪费了多少光阴
Watching their story, you realize how much time Richard and Ray spent on theories that made no sense.
Richard本可以用同样的时间去学习真实的历史，而不是虚构的时间立方体
Richard could have spent those same hours learning about actual history instead of imaginary timecubes.
而这正是这款电子游戏所能提供的
Which is exactly what this video game offers.
《战争雷霆》，本视频的赞助商，是有史以来内容最全面的载具战斗游戏
War Thunder, the sponsor of this video, is the most comprehensive vehicle combat game ever made.
这是一款拥有超过2500种坦克，飞机，直升机和舰船的大型多人在线游戏
It's an MMO featuring over 2,500 tanks, planes, helicopters, and ships.
从1920年代的装甲车到现代的战斗机和坦克，应有尽有
From armored cars of the 1920s to modern fighter jets and tanks.
这些载具的细节刻画非常到位，画面也超级逼真
The vehicles are very well detailed and the graphics are super realistic.
这款游戏一个与众不同之处在于它的伤害模型
Something that's really different about this game is its damage model.
如果你的或敌人的载具被摧毁，你会看到一个X光视角，可以清楚地看到炮弹击穿的位置以及哪些部件受到了影响
If your vehicle or enemy is destroyed, you see this x-ray view where you can see exactly where the shell penetrated and which components are affected.
老实说，这我以前从未见过
Which is honestly something I have never seen before.
《战争雷霆》有三种模式
War Thunder has three modes.
有适合快节奏比赛的街机模式
You have Arcade, which is for fast-paced matches.
历史模式，这个更贴近现实一些
Realistic mode, which is a bit more realistic.
还有最忠于现实的模式
Then you have the mode that is the most authentic to real life.
全真模拟模式
Simulator mode.
朋友们，今天就加入超过9500万玩家的社区，体验PVP战斗吧
My friends, join the community of over 95 million players for PvP battles today.
各位军事历史爱好者们，这款游戏就是为你们量身打造的
And for you military history enthusiasts, this game is made for you.
现在就通过置顶评论或描述中的链接，在PC，PlayStation，Xbox和移动设备上免费玩《战争雷霆》
Play War Thunder for free on PC, PlayStation, Xbox, and mobile now by using my link in the pinned comment or description.
新玩家和超过6个月未登录的老玩家都能获得一份丰厚的奖励包
New and returning players that haven't played in 6 months get a massive bonus pack.
其中包括“英勇之鹰”称号，10万银狮，以及7天高级账户，限时领取哦
That includes the Eagle of Valor, 100,000 silver lions, and 7 days of premium account only for a limited time.
下面这个神秘网站，神秘到黑客都想一探究竟
This next website was so mysterious that hackers tried to break into it.
Mortis.com
Mortis.com.
大多数网站都希望访客盈门
Most websites want visitors.
Mortis.com却恰恰相反
Mortis.com was the opposite.
它似乎想把所有人都拒之门外
It wanted to keep people out.
主页非常简洁
The home page was plain.
纯黑的背景上只有一个白色单词
Just a black screen with one word in white text.
Mortis
Mortis.
Mortis在拉丁语中意为“死亡”
Mortis means death in Latin.
谁会给自己的网站取名叫“死亡”呢
Why would anyone name their website death?
此外还有一个登录框，要求输入用户名和密码
There was also a login box asking for a username and password.
可要是没有账户，谁又能登录呢
But how could anyone sign in if they didn't have an account?
网站上没有注册按钮，没有创建账户的链接，根本无路可入
And there was no sign up button, no create account link, no way in at all.
就像一扇没有钥匙孔的紧锁大门
It was like a locked door with no keyhole.
多年来，这个网站就静静地待在那里
For years, the website just sat there.
没有更新，没有变化，没有任何活动的迹象
No updates, no changes, no sign of activity.
直到2011年，终于有人在4chan上提起了它
Then in 2011, someone finally mentioned it on 4chan.
有人成功进入过mortis.com吗
Did anyone ever get into mortis.com?
就这一个问题，让这个网站一夜爆红
That one question that made the site go viral.
4chan的用户们酷爱解谜，而这个谜题很快就让他们为之痴迷
4channers love puzzles, and this one quickly became an obsession.
首先，黑客们试图攻破mortis.com
First, hackers tried breaking into mortis.com.
但他们失败了
They couldn't.
接着，他们检查了网站的源代码
Then they examined the website's source code.
结果令人震惊
What they found was shocking.
一些单个文件的大小竟然高达39GB，而整个网站托管的数据总量达到了TB级别
Some of the individual files were as large as 39 gigabytes, and the total amount of data being hosted on the website was in the range of terabytes.
没人能想明白，一个没有任何公开功能的网站，为什么要存储如此海量的数据
No one could figure out why a website with no public features was storing that much data.
mortis.com究竟隐藏着什么
What was mortis.com hiding?
人们用尽了各种方法试图闯入，甚至动用了暴力破解程序
People tried everything to break in, even brute force applications.
但这个网站的防御固若金汤，于是他们转而查询域名记录，寻找网站的注册者
But the site was extremely hard to hack into, so they turned to domain records searching for whoever registered the site.
就在这时，他们发现了一个名字
That's when they discovered a name.
一连串线索让一些用户推断，该域名于1997年11月14日在一个名叫Thomas Ling的人名下注册
A string of clues led some users to assume that the domain was registered under the name Thomas Ling on the 14th of November, 1997.
他们开始深挖Thomas Ling的背景，希望能找到破解网站的新途径
They began digging into Thomas Ling, hoping to find new ways to unlock the website.
但无论他们怎么查，线索都断了
But no matter where they looked, the trail went nowhere.
更多关于Thomas Ling的线索最终都指向了全球各地偏远地区的空仓库
More leads on the Thomas Ling name would lead to empty warehouses in remote regions across the globe.
这个谜题似乎无解了
The mystery seemed unsolvable.
然而就在此时，Thomas Ling本人突然现身，而且他怒不可遏
Then suddenly Thomas Ling himself showed up, and he was mad.
Thomas找到了一个讨论mortis.com的聊天室，并警告所有人离他和他的网站远一点
Thomas found one of the chat rooms talking about mortis.com, and he told everyone to leave him and his site alone.
据说他要求用户停止尝试攻击他的网站，当被追问mortis.com的用途时，他声称该网站只是用来在线存放他的婚纱照
He allegedly demanded that the users stop trying to hack his website, and when pushed for an explanation on mortis.com, claimed that the website was only used to host his wedding photos online.
没人相信他就是真正的Thomas Ling
No one believed he was the real Thomas Ling.
为了证明自己确实是网站的主人，Thomas短暂地更改了mortis.com的主页
To prove he was really the man behind the site, Thomas briefly changed the home page of mortis.com.
然后又迅速地把它改了回来
Then, just as quickly, he switched it back.
这证实了他的所有者身份
That confirmed he was the owner.
但这丝毫没能解释那些庞大的文件和网站背后的谜团
But it did nothing to explain the massive files or the mystery behind the site.
终于，在2025年1月，有人揭开了谜底
Then, in January 2025, someone figured it out.
一篇题为《mortis.com之谜已解开》的Reddit帖子，揭示了登录界面背后的真相
A Reddit post titled, The mystery of the website mortis.com is solved, revealed what was really behind the login screen.
原来mortis.com是一个私人服务器，用于存储盗版电影和在一个小圈子内分享的大文件
Mortis.com was a private server for storing pirated movies and large files shared within a small group.
帖子甚至附上了截图，显示文件直接从该网站下载
The post even included screenshots showing downloads coming directly from the site.
在经历了15年的种种猜测之后，真相竟如此简单，令人大失所望
After 15 years of theories, the truth was disappointingly simple.
mortis.com并非什么黑暗的阴谋
Mortis.com wasn't a dark conspiracy.
它只是一个家伙和朋友们分享电影的地方
It was just a place where a guy shared movies with his friends.
接下来这个网站，可以用三个词来概括
This next website can be summed up in three words.
大失所望
A huge disappointment.
Zombo.com
Zombo.com.
Zombo.com的网页很奇怪
Zombo.com's webpage was strange.
它有一个绿色的背景，上面有旋转的圆圈
It had a green background with spinning circles.
但最诡异的是背景中播放的音频
But the weirdest part was the audio that played in the background.
在zombocom，你可以做任何事
You can do anything at yourself.
这声音听起来很鼓舞人心，好像有什么不可思议的事情即将发生
It sounded inspiring, like something incredible was about to happen.
但什么也没发生
But nothing ever did.
那个声音只是一遍又一遍地重复着同样的台词
The voice just repeated the same lines over and over.
没有链接，没有游戏，没有任何可下载的东西
There were no links, no games, nothing to download.
人们以为这个网站坏了
People thought the site was broken.
一位访客说，他等了五分钟，期待着什么，但网站始终没变
One visitor said they waited for five minutes for something to happen, but the site never changed.
后来，有人注意到了页面底部的时事通讯订阅链接
Then, someone noticed the newsletter sign up link at the bottom of the page.
总算有点能互动的东西了
Finally, something to interact with.
但他们注定要再次失望
But they were about to be disappointed.
点击链接后，会跳转到一个新页面，上面只有一行字
Clicking the link led to a new page with a single line of text.
抱歉，此功能暂不可用
Sorry, this is not working right now.
感谢您的耐心等待
Thanks for your patience.
用户们这才意识到，网站并没有坏
Users realized the site wasn't broken.
它就是被故意设计成这样的
It was built this way on purpose.
于是问题就变成了，是谁创建了Zombo.com，又是为什么
So the question became, who created Zombo.com and why?
2009年，网民们开始深挖这个网站的历史
In 2009, people online started digging into the site's history.
第一条线索来自网站的注册记录
The first clue came from the site's records.
查看Zombo.com的Whois记录，我们看到一个名叫Joshua Levine的人是域名注册人
When looking at the Whois record for Zombo.com, we can see someone by the name of Joshua Levine at the domain register.
现在他们有了一个名字，Joshua Levine
Now they had a name, Joshua Levine.
记录上甚至还列出了一个地址
The record even listed an address.
但当人们去查找时，却发现那只是某个小镇中央一片草地上的一个空长凳
But when people looked it up, it led to an empty bench in a little piece of grass in the middle of some tiny little town.
地址下列出的电话号码也没好到哪儿去
The phone number listed under the address was no better.
每次拨打都提示号码已停用
Every call ended with the line disconnected.
唯一有价值的线索来自Joshua Levine在2001年发出的一封电子邮件
The only meaningful clue came from an email Joshua Levine sent in 2001.
在邮件中，他解释说他的一个朋友用“Zombo”这个词来指代男性僵尸
In it, he explained that a friend of his used the word Zombo to refer to a male zombie.
所以他就用它作为了网站的名字
So he used it as the name of the site.
但这仍然没有解释Zombo.com存在的意义
But that still didn't explain the point of Zombo.com.
多年来，各种理论层出不穷
Over the years, theories piled up.
有人说，我认为Zombo.com是对互联网的一种戏仿
One person said, I think Zombo.com paraphrases the internet.
它向你许诺整个世界，但最终只给你一点动画
Promises you the earth, but delivers a bit of animation.
另一个人称该网站毫无用处，因为它除了告诉你它有多棒之外，什么也不做
Another called the site useless because it doesn't do anything except tell you how wonderful it is.
Zombo.com至今仍在运行
Zombo.com is still online today.
那些圆圈仍在旋转
The circles still spin.
那个声音仍在向你许诺无限的可能性
The voice still promises you limitless possibilities.
这真是一个奇妙的地方，一个什么都不会发生的地方
It's just a wonderful place where nothing ever happens.
如果你喜欢阴谋论，那你一定会爱上下面这个网站
If you love conspiracy theories, you'll love this next website.
SentimentalCorp.org
SentimentalCorp.org.
2012年，一个名叫Randy Prozac的男人推出了一个名为SentimentalCorp.org的网站
In 2012, a man named Randy Prozac launched a website called SentimentalCorp.org.
主页上是一对夫妇坐在沙发上看电视
The homepage showed a couple sitting on a couch watching TV.
屏幕上，“无物”一词隐约发光
On the screen, the word nothing glowed faintly.
但这个网站绝非“无物”
But the site was anything but nothing.
据Randy所说，他网站上的视频含有能控制思想的声音
According to Randy, the videos on his site contained sounds that could control minds.
要理解他为何有此想法，你得先了解Randy是何许人也
To understand why he believed that, you first have to know who Randy was.
在创办SentimentalCorp之前，Randy在加拿大阿尔伯塔省为精神病患者工作
Before SentimentalCorp, Randy worked with mental health patients in Alberta, Canada.
这些人都有着严重的心理问题
These were people with serious psychological issues.
他的目标是找到一种新的治疗方法
His goal was to find a new way to treat them.
于是他开始试验一种名为“心理剧”的疗法
That's when he began testing a form of therapy called psychodrama.
Randy每周三次邀请患者到他家中
Three times a week, Randy invited patients into his home.
在紧闭的门后，他们像舞台上的演员一样，将自己内心最深的恐惧和最黑暗的冲动表演出来
Behind closed doors, they acted out their deepest fears and darkest impulses like actors on a stage.
Randy录下了每一次治疗过程
Randy filmed every session.
很快，他便积累了数百小时令人不安的录像
Soon, he had hundreds of hours of disturbing footage.
但治疗过程的激烈程度超出了所有人的预料
But the sessions got more intense than anyone expected.
有时以泪水收场
Sometimes it ended in tears.
有时以愤怒告终
Sometimes it ended in anger.
有几次甚至演变成了暴力
A few times it ended in violence.
最终，这个项目失败了
Eventually, the program collapsed.
当局下令销毁Randy所有的录像带
Authorities ordered all of Randy's tapes destroyed.
但据报道，Randy在录像带被烧毁前，偷偷将它们带了出来
But Randy reportedly smuggled out the recordings before they could be burned.
这些录像带成为了SentimentalCorp.org的基础
Those tapes became the foundation of SentimentalCorp.org.
到2012年7月，Randy推出了他的网站，并开始上传心理剧治疗的录像
By July 2012, Randy launched his website and began uploading footage from the psychodrama sessions.
他还加上了一条令人不寒而栗的免责声明
He added a chilling disclaimer.
播放此心理音频磁带，您将接触到可能对认知人格造成永久性破坏的精神控制技术
By playing this psychological audio cassette, you would be exposed to mind control technology that may cause permanent destruction of cognitive personality.
但这警告非但没有吓跑人们，反而吸引了更多人
But instead of scaring people off, the warning only drew in more.
网站上有带有催眠声效和闪烁图像的视频
There were videos with hypnotic sounds and flashing imagery.
访客们形容其内容令人难以忘怀且极易上瘾
Visitors described the content as haunting and addictive.
有些人说看完后感到头晕目眩
Some said they felt dizzy after watching.
就连Randy本人也承认，你得是个魔术师才能玩转这个网站
Even Randy himself admitted that you would have to be a sort of a magician to navigate the site.
随着时间的推移，成千上万的人偶然发现了SentimentalCorp
Over time, thousands of people stumbled across SentimentalCorp.
网络论坛上充满了关于这些录像带，它们的目的，以及Randy精神控制说法的各种理论
Online forums filled with theories about the tapes, their purpose, and Randy's claims of mind control.
这个网站至今仍然存在
The site still exists today.
但许多心理剧的片段已经消失了
But many of the psychodrama clips have vanished.
没人知道是Randy自己删除了它们，还是发生了别的事情
No one knows whether Randy removed them himself or something else happened.
接下来这个网站，就是一个巨大的倒计时
This next website was one big countdown.
October282011.com，这个网站最早出现在2011年7月
October282011.com October282011.com first appeared in July 2011.
主页的标题写着，“梦中似曾相识”
The homepage had a heading that read, Deja Vu In Your Dreams.
标题下方是一只猫的插图
Beneath it was an illustration of a cat.
但真正吸引人眼球的是一个巨大的倒计时器
But what really grabbed people's attention was a giant countdown timer.
它被设定在2011年10月28日结束
It was set to end on October 28th, 2011.
没人知道2011年10月计时器归零时会发生什么，但他们决心要弄明白
No one knew what would happen when the timer hit zero in October 2011, but they were determined to figure it out.
各种理论开始涌现，尤其是在Reddit上
The theories started pouring in, especially on Reddit.
一些人相信这一天标志着世界末日
Some believed the date marked the end of the world.
另一些人则将其与宗教预言联系起来
Others tied it to a religious prophecy.
还有些人觉得这不过是一场营销噱头
Some felt it was part of a marketing stunt.
理论五花八门
The theories vary.
但所有人都一致认为
But everyone agreed.
2011年10月28日将有大事发生
Something big was coming on October 28th, 2011.
但网站上还有别的东西
But there was something else on the website.
主页底部附近有一个电话号码
Near the bottom of the homepage was a phone number.
不清楚这个号码是一开始就在那里，还是后来加上去的
It wasn't clear whether this number was there from the start or if it was added later.
号码旁边还有一行神秘的文字
Beside it was a cryptic line.
时机成熟时，开口即可开启
Speak to open when it's time.
很自然地，人们开始拨打这个号码
Naturally, people started calling.
他们反馈回来的情况令人不安
What they reported back was disturbing.
一位拨打者这样描述他的经历
One caller described this experience.
电话响了不到五声就有人接了
Someone answered within five rings.
没有问好，什么都没有
No hello, nothing.
只是一些动静，然后是一声响亮的哔声
Just some movement, and then a loud beep.
然后对方就挂了电话
And then the person hung up.
另一位则报告说听到有东西在地板上拖动的声音，随后是一声响亮的哔声
Another reported hearing something being dragged across the floor, followed by a loud beep.
当他们再次拨打时，有人接起电话低声说，又是他
When they called again, someone picked up and whispered, it's him again.
几乎所有尝试过这个号码的人都描述了一些令人不安的经历
Almost everyone who tried the number described something unsettling.
随着2011年10月28日的临近，人们的期待感越来越强
As October 28th, 2011 drew closer, anticipation was building.
倒计时即将归零
The countdown was almost at zero.
人们迫不及待地想看看会发生什么
And the people couldn't wait to see what would happen.
那一天终于到来了
The day finally arrived.
也确实发生了些什么
And something did happen.
但当2011年10月28日最终到来，倒计时归零时，网站却彻底消失了，让人们至今仍困惑不解
But when October 28th, 2011 finally came and the countdown hit zero, the site completely vanished, leaving people to this day in utter confusion.
网站就这么下线了
The website went offline just like that.
即使在网站消失后，人们仍在试图解开这个谜团
Even after the site disappeared, people kept trying to decode the mystery.
这个网站多年前就已下线，因此人们至今仍不清楚这背后是否真的有任何实际目的
The website went offline many years ago, and thus people have been left in the dark about whether or not this actually had any real purpose.
多年后，一位博主写了一篇题为《我想我解开了October282011.com背后的谜团》的文章
Years later, a blogger wrote an article titled, I think I solved the mystery behind October 28th, 2011.com.
他的解释平淡无奇
The explanation was underwhelming.
他声称这个网站只是为了吓唬人而制作的
He claimed the website was just made to freak people out.
而那些电话显然是旨在捉弄人的录音
And the calls were clearly recordings meant to mess with people's heads.
如今，输入October282011.com只会跳转到一些随机的广告页面
Today, typing in October 28th, 2011.com just redirects you to random ads.
接下来是另一个毫无逻辑可言的网站
Up next is another website that made zero sense.
Enrix.angelfire.com
Enrix.angelfire.com.
Enrix.angelfire.com描述了一种名为Enrix的疾病
Enrix.angelfire.com described a disease called Enrix.
它说，Enrix是一种可能对个人及其家庭成员造成毁灭性打击的疾病
It said, Enrix is a disease that can be devastating to an individual and their family members.
网站还提到了另一个术语，Gomex
The site also mentioned another term, Gomex.
Gomex是一个医学术语，常被患有Enrix的病人使用
Gomex is a medical term that's often used by patients suffering from Enrix.
但当人们用谷歌搜索这些疾病时，却一无所获
But when people Google these diseases, nothing came up.
Enrix和Gomex似乎并不存在
Enrix and Gomex don't seem to exist.
我试过用谷歌搜索这些疾病，但什么也找不到
I tried Google searching for these diseases, and I can't find anything about them.
这意味着有人围绕着不存在的疾病，建立了一个完整的医学网站
This meant someone built an entire medical website about illnesses that didn't exist.
但最奇怪的还不是这些虚构的疾病
But the fake diseases that weren't the strangest part.
真正的谜团是那张女人的照片
The real mystery was the woman's picture.
主页上有一张面带微笑，身着医生服饰的女性照片
On the homepage was a photo of a smiling woman dressed like a doctor.
点击她的脸会发生奇怪的事情
Clicking on her face did something strange.
如果你点击那张女人的照片，她的脸会变得略微扭曲
If you click on the picture of the woman, then the face will become slightly distorted.
继续点击，随着屏幕上所有文字变得错乱，她的脸也会变得更加扭曲
Continue clicking, and it will continue to become even more distorted as all the text on the screen becomes malformed.
每点击一次，照片的扭曲就更深一分
With every click, the photo warped further.
感觉就像网站正在实时崩溃
It looked like the site was falling apart in real time.
点击第五次时，一个诡异的笑脸出现了，还附带着一条信息
By the fifth click, a creepy smiley face appeared along with the message.
请醒来，并感谢您访问我们的网站
Please wake up and thank you for visiting our website.
这感觉不像是网站故障，更像是一个警告，让你停止探索
It felt less like a glitch and more like a warning to stop exploring.
但这仅仅是个开始
But that was just the beginning.
当人们查看其他页面时，发现了更怪异的东西
When people checked out the other pages, they found weird stuff.
一个页面上有一把巨大的蓝色钥匙
One page had a large blue key.
点击它只会把你送回主页
Clicking it only sent you back to the homepage.
代码中还埋藏着一个指向PDF文件的链接
There was also a link to a PDF file buried in the code.
那是一份长达634页的PDF文档，全部用泰语写成，其中还夹杂着一些卡通人物
It's a 634-page PDF document, all written in Thai, with cartoon characters at some points.
显然，这份PDF文件是关于一个根本不存在的心理健康热线诊所的
Apparently, this PDF file is about a mental health hotline clinic that doesn't actually exist.
接着出现了更奇怪的线索
Then came the Stranger's Clue.
一条隐藏的信息写着，梦境即将结束，Tyler
A hidden message that read, The dream is ending, Tyler.
Tyler是谁
Who's Tyler?
为什么他的名字会埋藏在乱码之中
And why was his name buried in scrambled text?
访客们还在网站上发现了这个隐藏的视频
Visitors also found this video hidden on the site.
当他们按下播放键，看到一个女人一边念着数字，一边画面不断出现故障
When they pressed play, they saw a woman glitching while reciting numbers.
人们挖得越深，就越觉得匪夷所思
The deeper people dug, the less sense it made.
2018年，一位名叫Foobans的推特用户承认是他创建了这个网站
In 2018, a Twitter user named Foobans admitted he created the site.
据他所说，整件事就是个恶作剧
According to him, the entire thing was a prank.
他制作这个网站是为了作为内部玩笑来捉弄和吓唬他的朋友
He made the site to troll and creep out his friend as an inside joke.
网站的每一部分，包括虚构的疾病，故障的图像和给Tyler的信息，都是一场大型的恶作剧
Every part of the site, including the fake diseases glitching images and Tyler messages, was a massive troll.
如今，原始网站已经消失了
Today, the original site is gone.
但它的镜像网站依然存在，让这个奇怪的恶作剧得以流传
But mirrors of it still exist, keeping the strange prank alive.
下面这个神秘网站，把自己的名字倒着拼写
This next mysterious website spelled its own name backward.
973-eht-namuh-973.com
973 at namu973.com.
你可能见过奇怪的网站名，但这个网站的名字简直是另一个境界
You've probably seen strange website names before, but this website name is on another level.
这个名字本身就是一个谜题
The name itself is a puzzle.
当倒着读时，它拼写为“the human”，即“人类”
When read backwards, it spells the human.
而谜团就从这里开始
And that's where the mystery begins.
主页用“迷宫中的咒语”这样的字眼欢迎访客
The homepage greets visitors with the words, Amaze in Abracadabra.
网站上的其他页面也并未让事情变得更清晰
The other pages on the site don't make things clearer.
有些页面上布满了奇怪的符号
There are pages with strange symbols.
另一个页面则展示了与数字和计算混合在一起的宗教经文
Another page displays religious passages mixed with numbers and calculations.
继续点击，你会偶然发现像这样令人不安的艺术作品
Keep clicking and you'll stumble upon disturbing artwork like this.
据报道，该网站包含超过9000个页面
The site reportedly contains more than 9,000 pages.
但没人能解释它存在的理由
But no one could explain why it even existed.
于是，互联网开始着手调查
So the internet began to investigate.
很快他们就查出了这个网站的创建者
And soon they found out who made this website.
这个网站是由一个名叫David Denison的人创建的
This website was created by a man named David Denison.
David曾经是个名人
David used to be famous.
在1970年代，Denison是英国最受欢迎的超现实主义画家之一
In the 1970s, Denison was one of the most popular surrealist painters in the United Kingdom.
在他的艺术生涯之后，David开始痴迷于数字和宗教
After his art career, David became obsessed with numbers and religion.
人们说，这种痴迷完全占据了他的整个生命
This obsession, people said, completely took over his being.
他整日沉浸在基于奇特词语和文本的计算中
He spent his days working through calculations based on strange words and texts.
许多内容都取自《圣经》和古代哲学家
Many were taken from the Bible and ancient philosophers.
他甚至对数字9和倒着拼写单词情有独钟
He was even obsessed with the number 9 and spelling words backwards.
2003年，David推出了他的终极创作，973-eht-namuh-973.com
In 2003, David launched his ultimate creation, 973 at namu973.com.
多年来，他不断为网站添加新页面
For years, he kept adding new pages to the website.
更多的谜题，更多的宗教文本，更多令人困惑的数学
More puzzles, more religious texts, more confusing math.
2013年，David Denison去世了
In 2013, David Denison passed away.
但网站却依然存在
But the website stayed alive.
在他去世前，David将网站的控制权交给了另一个人
Before he passed, David handed control of the site to someone else.
没人知道是谁
No one knows who.
在这位神秘看护人的管理下，网站的规模增长得更快了
Under this mystery caretaker, the site grew even faster.
成千上万的新页面出现了
Thousands of new pages appeared.
很快，一个虽小但极度痴迷的社群围绕着这个网站形成了
Soon, a small but obsessive community formed around the site.
甚至还有一个在线聊天室，人们在那里试图解读网站上奇怪图片，代码和计算背后的含义
There was even an online chat room where people tried to decode the meaning behind the weird pictures, codes, and calculations on the site.
直到有一天，有人解开了谜底
Then one day, someone figured it out.
2018年8月3日，一位名叫“白兔”的用户在聊天室发帖
On August 3rd, 2018, a user named White Rabbit posted in the chat room.
帖子标题是，《我终于解开了》
The post was titled, I finally solved it.
他说他花了至少五年时间研究这个网站
He said he spent at least five years studying the website.
而且他花了很多时间才引导自己走出这个迷宫
And that it took him a lot of hours to guide himself through the maze.
但在付出了所有努力之后，白兔声称他终于理解了网站上的谜题
But after all the work, White Rabbit claimed he finally understood the puzzles on the site.
但他不愿透露答案
But he wouldn't reveal the answer.
为什么
Why?
他说他发现的东西很危险
He said what he discovered was dangerous.
并且破解它对他的心智产生了奇怪的副作用
And that decoding it had strange side effects on his mind.
其他用户恳求他解释
Other users begged him to explain.
他再也没有回应
He never responded.
七年后，聊天室里另一位名叫“夏洛克”的人宣布了自己的突破
Seven years later, someone else in the chat room named Sherlock announced his own breakthrough.
我终于明白了
I finally understand it.
答案并非我所预期的
The answer is not what I expected.
但和白兔一样，夏洛克也拒绝分享他的解答
But like White Rabbit, Sherlock refused to share his solution.
他坚持认为每个人都必须自己找到答案
He insisted that everyone must find it on their own.
但他还是给了一条线索
But he didn't give them a clue.
答案并非直接写在网站上，而是通过字母，数字和象征符号来表达
The answer isn't written directly on the website itself, but rather written through letters, numbers, and representations.
从那以后，人们对这个网站更加痴迷了
From there, people got more obsessed with the site.
一位访客这样描述这个网站
One visitor described the site this way.
它就像一种毒品
It's like a drug.
一旦你解开一部分，你的大脑就会催促你继续下去
Once you solve one part, your brain tells you to keep going.
我聊过的一些人已经深陷其中
Some people I've been chatting with have lost it.
失去了与现实的联系
Lost touch with reality.
但我没有
Not me though.
我在应该停下的地方停下了
I stopped where I was supposed to stop.
我警告你，解码需自担风险
I warn you, decode at your own risk.
另一个人写道，这个网站是邪恶的
Another wrote the site is evil.
甚至有人声称这个网站会引起幻觉
Some even claim the site caused hallucinations.
今天，这个网站依然在线
Today the website is still online.
它有成千上万个页面
It has thousands of pages.
人们仍然在疯狂地试图破解它
And people are still going crazy trying to decode it.
这些网站不仅仅关乎隐藏的秘密
These sites aren't just about hidden secrets.
它们揭示了人性的某些方面
They show something about human nature.
我们渴望答案
We crave answers.
我们想要意义
We want meaning.
但有些兔子洞，实在太深了
But some rabbit holes go too deep.
朋友们，不是每个谜团都需要被解开
My friends, not every mystery needs solving.
而最明智的做法，就是知道何时该收手，我是Visual Venture
And the healthiest move is knowing when to stop visual venture.
请务必看看今天的赞助商，《战争雷霆》
Make sure you guys check out today's sponsor, War Thunder.
现在就通过下方链接，在PC，PlayStation，Xbox和移动设备上免费玩吧
Play it for free on PC, PlayStation, Xbox, and mobile now by using my link below.
新玩家和超过六个月未登录的老玩家将获得一份丰厚的奖励包
New and returning players that haven't played in six months will get a massive bonus pack.
如果你们喜欢这个视频，我们还介绍过更多奇怪的网站，其中一些真的相当令人不安
If you guys liked this video, we've covered plenty more strange websites and some of them are really disturbing.
要观看我这个系列关于“互联网上最令人不安的网站”的视频，请点击这里
To watch my video on this series, the most unsettling websites on the internet, click right here.
爱你们
Love you guys.
Peace!